Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Communications Department records, ca. 1970-2011
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Communications Department records, ca. 1970-2011
- Series IV. Photographs by Department
  - 008 Pharmacology, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 009 Physiology (folder 1), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 009 Physiology (folder 2), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 010 Preventative Medicine, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 011 Department of Clinical Sciences, Admininistration, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 012 Department of Clinical Sciences, Large Animal Surgery, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 013 Department of Clinical Sciences, Small Animal Surgery (folder 1), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 013 Department of Clinical Sciences, Small Animal Surgery (folder 2), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 014 Therio, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 015 Clinical Pathology, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 016 Radiology, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 017 Equine Research, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 018 Year Interns (folder 1), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 018 Year Interns (folder 2), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 019 Residents, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 020 Mastitis Research and Control, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 021 U.S. Nutrition Lab, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 022 Ambulatory, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 023 Agronomy, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 024Boyce Thompson Institute, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 025 Woodchucks, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 026 Equine Drug Testing, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 027 CRAR LAMS (Center for Research Animal Resources / Laboratory Animal Medicine), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 028 Epidemiology, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 029 Library, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 030 DCS Wildlife, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - AXT Interns, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Staff Photos, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Class Photos - 1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Class Photos - 1995 (folder 1) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Class Photos - 1995 (folder 2) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Class Photos - 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1974 Reunion Photos, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Telephone System Installation, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Series V. Ephemera
  - Centennial Medallions ( 2 ), 1994 (Box 7)